"Are ga shiritai" byou de ripurai riben no saisentan no jidai
"I want to know that," reply in seconds — the age at the cutting edge of convenience
Mamireru koukoku ya heitaa mo
Ads and haters all over,
sono yubi hitotsu de kantan ni kaiketsu desho
but just one tap of a finger and it's all resolved, right?
Demo kimi no mae ja fukisoku na rizumu kizami
But in front of you, my rhythm becomes erratic
Kore ja marude ikareta dooraa? Kimi wa misuterii?
Am I some broken dollar bot? Are you a mystery?
Matoi wa harusaki no yuki no you ni tokete yuku no
What I wear melts away like early spring snow
Kogareta purosesu de umareta sui? Amai? Nigai?
Is this craving born from a sweet? Bitter? Or what kind of process?
Ijou jitai da te ni oenai wa!
This is a crisis, it's out of control!
(CAN'T STOP)
Raddaddaddaito! Isso kowashite shimaitai no!
Raddaddaddite! I just want to break it all!
Mune no oku wo mushibamu wirusu no taishohou ga
This virus gnawing at my heart —
wakaranain da yo
— I don't know how to deal with it
Aitai no itai no tonde tte! One. Two. Three de tataite rouden
It hurts, I want to see you, fly away! Tap it out, 1-2-3, and I short-circuit
Biri biri da biri biri da DA
It tingles, it tingles, DA
GIDDY, GIDDY UP GIDDY, GIDDY UP, UP
Raddaddaddaito! Fureau tabi kawaru arugorizumu
Raddaddaddite! An algorithm that shifts each time we touch
"Anna no wa gijin da" nante kiben nya
"That's just anthropomorphism" — stuff that excuse,
marumete poi de odorimashou
let's toss it out and dance
UNDO wa shinaide konseiki saidai no machigai datte ii ne
No undo — even the biggest mistake of the century gets a like
LYLALYLALYLALYLALYLA...
Hajimete iki wo shita
I took my first breath